{"data":[{"question":"Dresses, skirts, shoes, and the children's clothing is advertised at reduced prices this weekend.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"children's clothing","b":"is advertised","c":"at","d":"prices","answer":"2","explain":" - Is advertised-> are advertised","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"24","subcategorylv2":"7","type":"1"},{"question":"Mary and her sister just bought two new winters coats at the clearance sale.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"her sister","b":"just bought","c":"two new","d":"winters","answer":"4","explain":" - Winters-> winter","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"24","subcategorylv2":"7","type":"1"},{"question":"A lunch of soup and sandwiches do not appeal to all of the students.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"A","b":"of","c":"do","d":"appeal to all of","answer":"3","explain":" Do-> does","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"24","subcategorylv2":"7","type":"1"},{"question":"Some of us have to study their lessons more carefully if we expect to pass this examination.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"have to","b":"their","c":"more carefully if","d":"to pass","answer":"2","explain":" - Their lessons-> these lessons","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"24","subcategorylv2":"7","type":"1"},{"question":"Mr. Peters used to think of hisself as the only president of the company.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"think","b":"hisself","c":"as the only","d":"of the company","answer":"2","explain":" -Hisself-> himself","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"24","subcategorylv2":"7","type":"1"},{"question":"This instructor advised the students for the procedures to follow in writing the term paper.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"for","b":"procedures","c":"follow","d":"in writing","answer":"1","explain":" - For-> on\nAdvise on: to be employed to give advice on a subject about which you have special knowledge or skill","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"24","subcategorylv2":"7","type":"1"},{"question":"Although both of them are trying to get the scholarship, she has the highest grades.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"of them","b":"are trying","c":"to get","d":"highest","answer":"4","explain":" - Highest-> higher","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"24","subcategorylv2":"7","type":"1"},{"question":"The new technique calls for heat the mixture before applying it to the wood.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"calls","b":"heat","c":"applying","d":"it to the wood","answer":"2","explain":" - Heat-> heating","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"24","subcategorylv2":"7","type":"1"},{"question":"The pilot and the crew distributed the life preservers between the twenty frantic passengers.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"and the crew","b":"distributed","c":"between","d":"frantic passengers","answer":"3","explain":" - Between-> among\/to\nDistribute something among\/to somebody","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"24","subcategorylv2":"7","type":"1"},{"question":"A five-thousand-dollars reward was offered for the capture of the escaped criminals.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"A","b":"dollars","c":"was offered","d":"for the capture of","answer":"2","explain":" - Dollars-> dollar","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"24","subcategorylv2":"7","type":"1"}]}